KEYUR J PRAJAPATI

@ keyur.01011988@gmail.com **+**91 9016073068

B - 100, Bhavnath society Near, Sayona City Ghatlodiya, Ahmedabad -380061

OBJECTIVE

To use the 10 years of experience I have gained in financial analysis, managing financial tasks and coming up with cost saving measures to enhance customer experience and build trust where I can utilize my expertise and learn more for organization's benefit which will also help to improve my career.

EXPERIENCE

IIFL FINANCE LTD 7th-Mar-2019 - 31st-Credit Manager

Jul-2020 Currently working in "IIFL FINANCE LTD" as a "CREDIT MANAGER" in SME department

since March-2019

Kotak Mahindra Bank 1st-Jul-

Credit Officer 2016 - 5th-

Mar-2019 Previously worked in crop loan division as Credit Officer.

All credit to pre-disbursement work like file checking, CAM sheet preparation,

pd. MIS maintain, co-ordination with sales team and FCU team.

Kotak Mahindra Bank 1st-Mar-

2013 - 30th-CPA

Worked in Personal Loan division as a CPA. Jun-2016

Payroll of "Ivangle sales and services"

Job Roll:

All credit to pre-disbursement work like file checking, CAM sheet preparation, MIS maintain, pre disbursement process, co-ordination with FI agencies and

FCU team.

HDFC Bank Ltd 1st-Aug-

2011 - 28th-CPA

Feb-2013 Worked in Two Wheeler Loan division as a CPA.

Payroll of "Sarvottam Consultant"

Job Roll:

All credit to pre-disbursement work like file checking, CAM sheet preparation,

MIS maintain, co-ordination with FI agencies and FCU team

EDUCATION

2011 **Gujarat University**

Graduation in Sociology

2006 G.S.H.E.B

H.S.C

1st class

2004 G.S.E.B

SSC

2nd class

SKILLS

Quick Grasping power

- Ability to communicate effectively with team members.
- Capacity to work in team or indivudualy and take up responsibility.

COMPUTER SKILLS

• I Have good command in MS Excel for vlookup, pivot etc.

LANGUAGE

- English
- Hindi
- Gujarati

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of Birth: 1st Jan 1988Martial status: Married

Cast : HinduGender : Male

HOBBIES

- Singing
- Travelling